(Sheldon:)Did I say Mars Rover?
(Leonard:)You did.
(Sheldon:)That was actually
a poorly chosen example,
(Sheldon:)as it had nothing
to do with me.
(Page:)Yes, well, let's talk
about it anyway.
(Raj:)I don't want to.
(Sheldon:)Not that my disinclination
(Sheldon:)to discuss the topic
should be interpreted as
(Sheldon:)evidence of Howard Wolowitz's
culpability in the destruction
(Sheldon:)of government property
worth millions of dollars.
(Page:)Thank you, Dr. Cooper.
(Page:)I think I have all I need.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good.
(Sheldon:)I was afraid you were
going to fixate
(Sheldon:)on that Mars Rover incident.
(Howard:)Hey, buddies.
(Howard:)Guess who didn't get
security clearance
(Howard:)to work on
the giant space laser?
(Leonard:)What happened?
(Howard:)Apparently, the background
interviews didn't go well.
(Howard:)You guys wouldn't
know anything
(Howard:)about that, would you?
(Raj:)Well, actually,
I may have gotten
(Raj:)a little tipsy
when I talked to her.
(Leonard:)And I may have
(Leonard:)hit on her a little bit.
(Raj:)I may have thrown up
rum cake on her shoes.